<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tobias Wilker</title>
    <description>From electrical engineering to a decade in C#, my journey led me to the marvels of Web 3.0, unlocking superpowers in full-stack and blockchain development.</description>
    <link>https://twilker.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://twilker.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:06:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>Pioneering a Modular Web Platform: A Journey into Flexibility &amp; Performance</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-genesis&quot;&gt;Project Genesis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving realm of software development, the need for platforms that can host a myriad of distinct applications becomes paramount. With this mission in mind, we embarked on an ambitious journey to create a web platform designed for utmost modularity, ensuring easy integration and extension of various applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;taking-the-helm-roles--responsibilities&quot;&gt;Taking the Helm: Roles &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the core team driving this endeavor, my role encompassed forging a path to a sustainable system architecture and laying foundational processes, particularly in areas like CI/CD. A pivotal moment was when I led the creation of a prototype—a tangible proof of concept that encapsulated our vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;innovations--challenges&quot;&gt;Innovations &amp;amp; Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the significant innovations was developing a new template system—a testament to past experiences and learnings. This system is not only more flexible than previous incarnations but also boasts an inherent ease of use and extensibility. To bolster the template language, I devised a simplistic expression language, ensuring that even in potential corruption scenarios, the system remains secure by design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the path hasn’t been without its fair share of challenges. One recurring theme has been aligning perspectives. Engaging with colleagues from a predominantly desktop application background meant frequent discussions rooted in desktop paradigms, which often required reorientation for the web domain. It became a balance of discussion and education, merging past experiences with future possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tech-stack--team-synergy&quot;&gt;Tech Stack &amp;amp; Team Synergy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Angular has been chosen for the frontend, owing to its robust micro frontend support that facilitates a seamless plugin interface, the backend remains a playground. We’re currently experimenting with various languages and frameworks, striving to find the perfect fit for our unique performance needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team, comprising ten developers, operates on a democratic ethos. Although a group of experts prepares critical decisions, inclusive discussions involving the entire team are integral to our decision-making process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;looking-ahead&quot;&gt;Looking Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project, still in its developmental phase, promises to build a web platform that lasts for decades. The journey, laden with innovations, challenges, and collective growth, paints a picture of a future where adaptability is not just desired but inherently built-in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/work/web-platform/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/work/web-platform/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LumiOS - We Illuminate Your Life</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;inspiration&quot;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project, Illuminate, was born from my vision to advance the AI revolution and make AI an integral part of daily life. My dissatisfaction with current AI implementations and their superficial integration with our day-to-day applications led me to dream bigger. The movie ‘Her’ served as a key inspiration, captivating me with its portrayal of technological advancement through minimalistic and pure form of interaction - speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;building-the-project&quot;&gt;Building the Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working on Illuminate’s core, LumiOS, I seek to actualize this vision. The goal is to create a personal AI combined with an AI operating system, capable of retaining all our interactions and integrating seamlessly with various applications. This project provides a perfect platform for me to expand my knowledge in Flutter and NestJS. While using Flutter for building the frontend, I delved into the intricacies of Riverpod’s provider system. Meanwhile, NestJS allowed me to experiment with a new architectural design, combining Domain Driven Design, Clean Architecture, and Event Driven Architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenges&quot;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The journey was not without its fair share of challenges. Issues with websocket instabilities provided significant hurdles, as did the steep learning curve associated with setting up a Continuous Deployment pipeline using Google Cloud and GitHub actions. These experiences, though testing, contributed immensely to my growth as a developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reflection&quot;&gt;Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite these obstacles, the overwhelming realization was that the vision of LumiOS is very much achievable with current technologies. This project has reinforced my belief that we are on the cusp of a radical transformation in the way we interact with technology, a transformation that will redefine our experiences in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-next-for-lumios&quot;&gt;What’s Next for LumiOS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey of LumiOS is far from complete. My next big step is to introduce a speech interface to enhance user interaction, following which I plan on expanding its capabilities further. This includes adding access to emails, calendars, and the internet for research purposes, moving beyond the constraints of a mere chat-based interface. The ultimate goal is to continue to build on this idea, to drive deeper integration and create an AI that truly understands and complements the user’s lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/projects/lumios/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/projects/lumios/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Navigating Rust: Implementing Chum Pederson ZKP</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-challenge-a-race-against-time&quot;&gt;The Challenge: A Race Against Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of a rigorous job interview process, I embarked on an ambitious task: implementing the Chum Pederson Zero-Knowledge Proof (ZKP) for authentication in Rust. With a tight deadline of one week, I set out to complete the project, delivering it in just 2.5 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rusts-unique-challenge-object-ownership&quot;&gt;Rust’s Unique Challenge: Object Ownership&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary hurdle in this project was Rust’s unique approach to object ownership and memory management. Coming from a background predominantly focused on smart contracts, this presented a new complexity level. My solution, under the time pressure, involved an extensive use of locks to manage object ownership – a practical but suboptimal approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;focus-on-comprehensive-development&quot;&gt;Focus on Comprehensive Development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aware of the constraints and priorities, I chose to allocate my time effectively. While the locking mechanism was a quick-fix, I invested significant effort into other aspects of the project, such as thorough documentation, rigorous testing, and Dockerization. This holistic approach ensured the project was well-rounded and ready for practical deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;feedback-and-learning&quot;&gt;Feedback and Learning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project culminated in an in-depth discussion with the interviewers about the locking issue I encountered. This feedback session was as much a learning opportunity as it was an evaluation, highlighting the importance of balancing quick solutions with optimal practices, especially under time constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experience was more than just a technical challenge; it was a testament to adaptive learning and strategic prioritization under pressure. It underscored the importance of understanding and navigating a language’s unique features, like Rust’s object ownership model, and the value of comprehensive development, even when racing against the clock.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/projects/cp-zkp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/projects/cp-zkp/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bridging Blockchain &amp; Backend: My Dynamic Stint at AgreeWe</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embarking on a freelance journey with AgreeWe, I dove headfirst into the bustling startup environment. A short but insightful 4-month experience, the role was both challenging and exhilarating, fueling my passion and introducing me to new horizons in the tech landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rapid-integration--key-achievements&quot;&gt;Rapid Integration &amp;amp; Key Achievements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my standout moments at AgreeWe was the prototypical integration of a new smart contract. With a keen understanding of the backend architecture, I managed to seamlessly incorporate the changes in just a few hours over a weekend. The swiftness and efficiency of this integration is something I take great pride in, showcasing my adaptability and quick comprehension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenges-faced&quot;&gt;Challenges Faced&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While technical challenges are par for the course, sometimes the interpersonal ones are trickier. Taking over from another blockchain developer, unbeknownst to him that I was stepping into his shoes, made our interactions a tad awkward. Such scenarios underlined the importance of transparent communication and tact in professional transitions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;learning--development&quot;&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diving deeper into NestJS, this role facilitated my exploration of its advanced concepts. I acquainted myself with sophisticated features such as pipes and custom guards, enhancing my backend expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;embracing-global-collaboration&quot;&gt;Embracing Global Collaboration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AgreeWe’s team was an eclectic mix of talents, operating remotely across the globe. Transitioning from predominantly German teams to this diverse, worldwide group was an eye-opener. While it necessitated more regular communication for synchronization, the collaboration was smooth, offering a glimpse into the future of global remote work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though brief, my time at AgreeWe was a whirlwind of learning, challenges, and accomplishments. It reiterated the significance of adaptability in the tech domain and broadened my perspective on global teamwork. As I continue on my professional journey, the insights garnered here, especially the interplay between different architectural approaches, enrich my subsequent endeavors like LumiOS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/work/agreewe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/work/agreewe/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building an Open-Source CLI for Cross Compiling: Leading &amp; Innovating at Phoenix Contact</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-overview&quot;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stepping into a lead developer role at Phoenix Contact, I helmed a compact but dynamic team in creating a CLI interface tailored for cross compiling C++ applications for PLCnext controllers. This CLI, now open-source, stands as a testament to our collective endeavor and innovation in streamlining development processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenges--technical-triumphs&quot;&gt;Challenges &amp;amp; Technical Triumphs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most intricate tasks was crafting an extensible template system. Through this, C++ projects could be seamlessly initialized, and during the build phase, boilerplate code was auto-generated. This required a novel solution: creating a C++ parser from scratch based on a rudimentary grammar I stumbled upon. It was a foray into uncharted territory, and the result was a powerful tool that enhanced our CLI’s capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;collaborative-dynamics--leadership&quot;&gt;Collaborative Dynamics &amp;amp; Leadership&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our close-knit team comprised three developers and two testers. The close proximity of our workspaces facilitated frequent communication, allowing us to swiftly address concerns, feedback, and reviews. By demarcating specific areas for each team member, we ensured focused contributions and maintained a steady project pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Half a year was what it took to roll out the initial version, but I continued my journey as the lead engineer for three more years. During this tenure, the CLI underwent substantial architectural enhancements, reflecting our commitment to continuous improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reception--continuous-enhancement&quot;&gt;Reception &amp;amp; Continuous Enhancement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, our CLI finds its place in the toolkits of numerous users and enjoys the distinction of being open source. Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive. We’ve been graced with constructive improvement suggestions from the user community, which we’ve been proactive in implementing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reflections&quot;&gt;Reflections&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One profound lesson this journey imparted was the significance of early communication, especially concerning innovative ideas. I spent considerable time working on an event-driven architecture without initiating preliminary discussions. The eventual feedback made it clear that it wasn’t the right fit for our product. This reinforced the importance of early ideation sharing to align with team and project goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project was more than just developing a tool; it was about leading a talented team, innovating continuously, and most importantly, learning from every step of the journey.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/work/plcnext-cli/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/work/plcnext-cli/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEAR Spring Hackathon 2022</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;embracing-the-challenge&quot;&gt;Embracing the Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NEAR Spring Hackathon 2022 presented an exhilarating challenge: to develop eight distinct decentralized applications (dApps) over four weeks. This was not just a test of skill and creativity but also an endurance challenge, focusing on learning and adapting to the NEAR blockchain ecosystem and smart contract development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;innovative-dapps-for-social-good&quot;&gt;Innovative dApps for Social Good&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the dApps I developed, two stood out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rewarding Social Good:&lt;/strong&gt; This app was designed to incentivize socially beneficial actions. Users could upload proof of their good deeds, ranging from helping the homeless to assisting the elderly. The platform enabled other users to reward these deeds with NEAR tokens.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aiding Ukrainian Zoos:&lt;/strong&gt; Amidst the Ukrainian war, zoos were struggling. I created a gacha game where users collected sets of zoo animal NFTs. A portion of the NFT sales was allocated to a dedicated wallet for zoo donations, while the remainder formed a jackpot. Collecting a complete set entitled users to win 50% of the current jackpot, making it a strategic and charitable endeavor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;personal-growth-and-learning&quot;&gt;Personal Growth and Learning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hackathon was a deep dive into uncharted territories for me. Prior to this event, my experience in web development, especially with modern technologies like React, was minimal. I was not only learning to craft NEAR smart contracts with Rust but simultaneously mastering React for frontend development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;outcome-and-reflection&quot;&gt;Outcome and Reflection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hard work paid off – I emerged as one of the two winners of the hackathon. This victory, however, was more than just a title. It was a testament to the joy and fulfillment I found in dApp development. Nevertheless, the intensity of these four weeks, balanced alongside full-time work, taught me the importance of pacing myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;future-directions&quot;&gt;Future Directions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experience catalyzed a significant shift in my professional focus – from C# to web 2.0/3.0 technologies. It marked the beginning of a new chapter in my career, steering me towards a future rich in web technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/projects/near-spring-hackathon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/projects/near-spring-hackathon/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Redefining Data Storage at Phoenix Contact: A Test-Driven Journey</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-overview&quot;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Senior Developer at Phoenix Contact, I was handed the reins to overhaul our data storage layer. The existing system had become a bottleneck, unable to adapt to emerging requirements. This gave me the opportunity to apply Test-Driven Development (TDD) for the first time in a substantial project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-challenge-understanding-legacy-code&quot;&gt;The Challenge: Understanding Legacy Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most daunting aspect was to identify existing functionalities due to the lack of documentation. Navigating through legacy code to understand its nuances was critical for a smooth transition to a new storage layer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;finding-the-right-architecture&quot;&gt;Finding the Right Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having mapped out the existing functionalities, the next step was to architect a flexible and scalable data storage layer. Although the chosen architecture has served well over time, retrospection suggests room for improvements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-role-of-test-driven-development-tdd&quot;&gt;The Role of Test-Driven Development (TDD)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Utilizing TDD was groundbreaking for me. The methodology allowed me to develop the new storage layer blindly—without any manual tests—for weeks. Subsequent integration took merely days, validating the strength of a test-first approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lessons-learned&quot;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Power of TDD:&lt;/strong&gt; One of the major revelations was recognizing how TDD can facilitate the development of complex features that are not easily testable manually.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evolving Architectural Insights:&lt;/strong&gt; The perception of ‘good architecture’ evolves approximately every three years. What appears optimum today may become obsolete tomorrow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ongoing-contributions-and-team-training&quot;&gt;Ongoing Contributions and Team Training&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-implementation, my role transitioned to continually augmenting the storage layer to meet new requirements. Concurrently, I took the initiative to train team members in testing methodologies, sharing the expertise I had garnered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;future-directions&quot;&gt;Future Directions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the storage layer has proven resilient, its growing complexity over time has made replacement challenging. This underscores the need for continued innovation in architectural decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was an enlightening experience, validating the utility of TDD and underlining the evolving nature of software architecture. It has also provided me valuable lessons that continue to shape my approach to software development.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/work/data-storage-pcwx/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/work/data-storage-pcwx/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Refactoring Phoenix Contact's Graphical Editor: Embracing Testability &amp; Extensibility</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-overview&quot;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Phoenix Contact, I was entrusted with refining an existing graphical editor. My colleague had initiated the development, and an MVP was in place. My journey began by acquainting myself with the editor and recognizing potential avenues for improvement, especially in terms of testability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-challenges&quot;&gt;The Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the foundation of the editor was robust, its architecture didn’t support testability. Object creation was intertwined with dependency management, making it a challenge to implement efficient unit tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-role--approach&quot;&gt;My Role &amp;amp; Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;implementing-inversion-of-control-ioc&quot;&gt;Implementing Inversion of Control (IoC)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address the testability challenge, my primary objective was to restructure the application by introducing IoC. This design pattern ensured that objects received their dependencies from outside rather than creating them internally, a change pivotal in enabling unit testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;testing-framework-development&quot;&gt;Testing Framework Development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post-restructuring, I developed a comprehensive testing framework. This involved both traditional unit tests and Behavior-Driven Development (BDD) style tests using SpecFlow. This layered testing approach ensured thorough coverage and efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;additional-responsibilities&quot;&gt;Additional Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I delved deeper into the project:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feature Expansion&lt;/strong&gt;: I continually added new functionalities to the editor, like crafting routing algorithms.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SFC Editor Creation&lt;/strong&gt;: Drawing from the primary editor, I spearheaded the development of a new editor tailored for Sequential Function Chart (SFC). The central challenge here was devising an automatic arrangement algorithm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;outcomes--legacy&quot;&gt;Outcomes &amp;amp; Legacy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The refactored editor base, enhanced for testability and extensibility, became a cornerstone within our framework. Various editors within the ecosystem have since been built upon this foundational architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reflections--lessons-learned&quot;&gt;Reflections &amp;amp; Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project offered profound insights. Most notably, I discerned that unit tests might not always be the optimal choice, especially when the inner architecture is in flux. Integration tests, particularly with tools like SpecFlow, provide unparalleled reliability in such scenarios. Today, my testing strategy revolves around unit tests for high-permutation classes, like algorithms, while leaning on integration tests for broader functionalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;future-directions&quot;&gt;Future Directions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I’ve transitioned from the project, further refinements have been made post my tenure. These enhancements focused on eliminating architectural inefficiencies and bolstering code readability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project at Phoenix Contact was a testament to the importance of adaptability in software engineering. While established systems offer a foundation, continual introspection and restructuring pave the way for optimization, ensuring the software’s longevity and efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://twilker.github.io/work/graphical-editor/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://twilker.github.io/work/graphical-editor/</guid>
      </item>
    

  </channel>
</rss>